const football = [{id: 1, question: "What is Charlton Athletics nickname?", options: ["The Reds", "The Addicks", "Red Robins", "Eagles"], correct_answer: "The Addicks"}, {id: 2, question: "Who is the all time leading goalscorer in the Premier League?", options: ["Alan Shearer", "Thierry Henry", "Wayne Rooney", "Didier Drogba"], correct_answer: "Alan Shearer"}, {id: 3, question: "Which team has the lowest points total in Premier League history?", options: ["Watford", "Norwich", "Derby", "Sunderland"], correct_answer: "Derby"}, {id: 4, question: "Who was the Premier Leagues top scorer in the 2017/18 season?", options: ["Jamie Vardy", "Harry Kane", "Sergio Aguero", "Marcus Rashford"], correct_answer: "Harry Kane"}, {id: 5, question: "Which teams were promoted to the Premier League in 18/19 season?", options: ["Norwich, Bournemouth, Leeds", "Aston Villa, Sheffield United, West Brom", "Middlesbrough, Sheffield United, Fulham", "Norwich, Sheffield United, Aston Villa"], correct_answer: "Norwich, Sheffield United, Aston Villa"}] 

const mma = [{id: 1, question: "Who has the most title defences in UFC history?", options: ["Demetrious Johnson", "Anderson Silva", "Jon Jones", "Georges St Pierre"], correct_answer: "Demetrious Johnson"}, {id: 2, question: "Who was the first double champion in UFC history?", options: ["Amanda Nunes", "Daniel Cormier", "Conor McGregor", "Georges St Pierre"], correct_answer: "Conor McGregor"}, {id: 3, question: "Who is the youngest person to win a UFC Championship?", options: ["Valentina Shevchenko", "Jon Jones", "Petr Yan", "Kamuru Usman"], correct_answer: "Jon Jones"}, {id: 4, question: "Who has the most knock outs in UFC history?", options: ["Derrick Lewis", "Francis Ngannou", "Michael Bisping", "Matt Brown"], correct_answer: "Derrick Lewis"}, {id: 5, question: "Who has/had the nickname Funky?", options: ["Alex Volkanovski", "Colby Covington", "Ben Askren", "Diego Sanchez"], correct_answer: "Ben Askren"}]
     
const games = [{id: 1, question: "What is the biggest selling game of all time?", options: ["Red Dead Redemption 2", "GTA V", "The Legend of Zelda Breathe of the Wild", "Call of Duty Modern Warefare 2"], correct_answer: "GTA V"}, {id: 2, question: "Which is of these games is made by SuckerPunch studios?", options: ["Far Cry 6", "Cyberpunk 2077", "Ghost of Tsushima", "Horizon Forbidden West"], correct_answer: "Ghost of Tsushima"}, {id: 3, question: "In what year was the Xbox 360 released?", options: ["2005", "2006", "2008", "2010"], correct_answer: "2005"}, {id: 4, question: "How many games are in the Uncharted series?", options: ["4", "3", "5", "6"], correct_answer: "5"}, {id: 5, question: "What is the name of the main protagonist in God of War?", options: ["Plato", "Atreus", "Kratos", "Loki"], correct_answer: "Kratos"}]

export {football, mma, games}